   [
     {
       "questionId": "1",
       "questionText": "What is the purpose of ear wax?",
       "optionOne" : "To protect your ear",
       "optionTwo" : "To make candles",
       "optionThree" : "No use at all",
       "optionFour"  : "None of the above",
       "correctAnswer" : "1",
       "explanation"  :"Provides  lubrication and protection against bacteria",
       "grade" : "2",
       "categoryId" : "10",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     {
       "questionId": "2",
       "questionText": "What is a scientist called that studies sound?",
       "optionOne" : "Meteorologist",
       "optionTwo" : "Acoustical Engineer",
       "optionThree" : "Entomologist",
       "optionFour"  : "Paleontologist",
       "correctAnswer" : "2",
       "explanation"  :"They deal with sound and vibration",
       "grade" : "2",
       "categoryId" : "10",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     {
       "questionId": "3",
       "questionText": "An instrument to measure temperature is called ?",
       "optionOne" : "Hydrometer",
       "optionTwo" : "Thermometer",
       "optionThree" : "Gyrometer",
       "optionFour"  : "Thermometer",
       "correctAnswer" : "2",
       "explanation"  :"Its temperature sensor element helps to measure body temperature",
       "grade" : "2",
       "categoryId" : "10",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     {
       "questionId": "4",
       "questionText": "Another name for a twister is ?",
       "optionOne" : "Earthquake",
       "optionTwo" : "Tornado",
       "optionThree" : "Wind",
       "optionFour"  : "Flood",
       "correctAnswer" : "2",
       "explanation"  :"A tornado is a violently rotating column of air",
       "grade" : "2",
       "categoryId" : "10",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     {
       "questionId": "5",
       "questionText": "It is a bird born out of the largest egg in the world?",
       "optionOne" : "Sparrow",
       "optionTwo" : "Hen",
       "optionThree" : "Turkey",
       "optionFour"  : "Ostrich",
       "correctAnswer" : "4",
       "explanation"  :"They are native to Africa",
       "grade" : "2",
       "categoryId" : "10",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     {
       "questionId": "6",
       "questionText": "Which planet is called the Red Planet?",
       "optionOne" : "Mars",
       "optionTwo" : "Venus",
       "optionThree" : "Mercury",
       "optionFour"  : "Jupiter",
       "correctAnswer" : "1",
       "explanation"  :"Mars is often called the 'Red Planet' because it appears in the sky as an orange-red star.",
       "grade" : "2",
       "categoryId" : "10",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     {
       "questionId": "7",
       "questionText": "Albatross is?",
       "optionOne" : "A sea bird",
       "optionTwo" : "A beetle",
       "optionThree" : "A fruit",
       "optionFour"  : "A city",
       "correctAnswer" : "1",
       "explanation"  : "The name albatross is derived from the Arabic",
       "grade" : "2",
       "categoryId" : "10",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     {
       "questionId": "8",
       "questionText": "It bears the closest resemblance to man?",
       "optionOne" : "Panda",
       "optionTwo" : "Rhino",
       "optionThree" : "Chimpanzee",
       "optionFour"  : "Elephant",
       "correctAnswer" : "3",
       "explanation"  : "Chimpanzees are an exclusively African species",
       "grade" : "2",
       "categoryId" : "10",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     {
       "questionId": "9",
       "questionText": "It is known as the ship of the desert?",
       "optionOne" : "Cat",
       "optionTwo" : "Camel",
       "optionThree" : "Panther",
       "optionFour"  : "Rabbit",
       "correctAnswer" : "2",
       "explanation"  : "The name is because of their ability to consume very little water without dehydrating.",
       "grade" : "2",
       "categoryId" : "10",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     {
       "questionId": "10",
       "questionText": "How much is 132+244?",
       "optionOne" : "183",
       "optionTwo" : "376",
       "optionThree" : "278",
       "optionFour"  : "",
       "correctAnswer" : "2",
       "explanation"  : "",
       "grade" : "2",
       "categoryId" : "1",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     {
       "questionId": "11",
       "questionText": "How much is 623+135?",
       "optionOne" : "658",
       "optionTwo" : "358",
       "optionThree" : "758",
       "optionFour"  : "",
       "correctAnswer" : "3",
       "explanation"  : "",
       "grade" : "2",
       "categoryId" : "1",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     {
       "questionId": "12",
       "questionText": "How much is 244+208?",
       "optionOne" : "183",
       "optionTwo" : "376",
       "optionThree" : "278",
       "optionFour"  : "452",
       "correctAnswer" : "4",
       "grade" : "2",
       "explanation"  : "",
       "categoryId" : "1",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     {
       "questionId": "13",
       "questionText": "How much is 135+403?",
       "optionOne" : "847",
       "optionTwo" : "538",
       "optionThree" : "",
       "optionFour"  : "",
       "correctAnswer" : "2",
       "explanation"  : "",
       "grade" : "2",
       "categoryId" : "1",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     {
       "questionId": "14",
       "questionText": "How much is 321+425?",
       "optionOne" : "630",
       "optionTwo" : "720",
       "optionThree" : "860",
       "optionFour"  : "746",
       "correctAnswer" : "4",
       "explanation"  : "",
       "grade" : "2",
       "categoryId" : "1",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     { "questionId": "15",
       "questionText": "If red and blue color is mixed what color it forms?",
       "optionOne" : "purple",
       "optionTwo" : "orange",
       "optionThree" : "green",
       "optionFour"  : "",
       "correctAnswer" : "1",
       "explanation"  : "",
       "grade" : "0",
       "categoryId" : "14",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     { "questionId": "16",
       "questionText": "If yellow and blue color is mixed what color it forms?",
       "optionOne" : "purple",
       "optionTwo" : "orange",
       "optionThree" : "green",
       "optionFour"  : "",
       "correctAnswer" : "3",
       "explanation"  : "",
       "grade" : "0",
       "categoryId" : "14",
       "userid" : "1"
     },
     { "questionId": "17",
       "questionText": "If red and yellow color is mixed what color it forms?",
       "optionOne" : "purple",
       "optionTwo" : "orange",
       "optionThree" : "green",
       "optionFour"  : "",
       "correctAnswer" : "2",
       "explanation"  : "",
       "grade" : "0",
       "categoryId" : "14",
       "userid" : "1"
     }
   ]